{"metadata":{"generator":"Captivate","generatorVersion":"10.0.0","schemaVersion":"","author":"author","title":"","description":"project description","email":"author@company.com","website":"www.company.com","tags":"","thumbnail":"","source":"assets","durationInFrames":1668,"frameRate":30,"totalSlides":17,"width":1024,"height":627,"responsive":false,"scalable":true,"launchFile":"index.html"},"contentStructure":[{"id":"Image_4","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_4","roles":{}},{"id":"SmartShape_2","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_2","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_3","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_3","title":"Scenario: Root Cause Analysis ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_2","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_2","roles":{}},{"id":"Text_Caption_3","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_3","title":"Length: 8 minutes ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_4","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_4","title":"This CE program was developed for the following grant: Primary Care Nurse Practitioner Preceptor Development Program (PC-NP-PDP)  HRSA GRANT # D09HP29976  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Line_1","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Line_1","roles":{}},{"id":"SmartShape_4","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_4","title":"Start ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9945","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Start ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9966","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Start ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_132","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_132","title":"1 / 17 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide9896","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"Introduction","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_4","SmartShape_2","Image_2","Text_Caption_3","Text_Caption_4","SmartShape_4","si9945","si9966","Text_Caption_132"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":228},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide9896"}}},{"id":"si9990","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10001","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"f ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10012","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"g ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10023","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"____ ____ ____ ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10034","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si10058","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Scenario: Root Cause Analysis ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_124","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_124","title":"Click here if video does not load ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Web_1","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Web_1","roles":{}},{"id":"SmartShape_48","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_48","title":"Return to last slide visited ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si14850","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Return to last slide visited ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si14870","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Return to last slide visited ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_133","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_133","title":"2 / 17 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide9973","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"Correct Scenario","thumbnail":"","children":["si9990","si10001","si10012","si10023","si10034","si10058","Text_Caption_124","SmartShape_48","si14850","si14870","Text_Caption_133"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide9973"}}},{"id":"si5613","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide10103q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5626","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide10103q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5639","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"f ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide10103q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5666","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"____ ____ ____ ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide10103q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5672","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si10070","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Scenario: Root Cause Analysis ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10116","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide10103q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10127","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"g ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide10103q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_50","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_50","title":"Conducting or Participating in a Root Cause Analysis ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_49","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_49","title":"View Scenario ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide10103q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si14887","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"View Scenario ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide10103q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si14899","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"View Scenario ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide10103q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_134","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_134","title":"3 / 17 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10161","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You have completed watching a video on one of several formats for conducting a Root Cause Analysis.  Based on the statement by the ‘nurse’ in the scenario: “Our high volume of scheduled patients, and then walk-in sick visits are a set up for errors without a specific plan.”  Determine which step of a Root Cause Analysis process was performed by the nurse? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10176","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10180","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Identify what happened ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10176_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Identify what happened\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si10187","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10191","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"What should have happened ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10187_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"What should have happened\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si10257","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10261","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Write a summary ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10257_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Write a summary\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si10272","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10276","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Recommendations ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10272_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Recommendations\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si10195","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide10103q0","for":"Slide10103q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10212","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide10103q0","for":"Slide10103q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10225","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide10103q0","for":"Slide10103q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10280","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct - The high volume of patients and walk-in sick patients without a plan in place to perform and document PPD readings is what happened.   Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide10103q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10293","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"The correct answer is A - The high volume of patients and walk-in sick patients without a plan in place to perform and document PPD readings is what happened.   Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide10103q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si15934","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide10103q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide10103","class":"Question Slide","instance":"Question 1","thumbnail":"","children":["si5613","si5626","si5639","si5666","si5672","si10070","si10116","si10127","Text_Caption_50","SmartShape_49","si14887","si14899","Text_Caption_134","si10161","si10180","si10191","si10261","si10276","si10195","si10212","si10225","si15934"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide10103"},"question":{"interactionId":"10141","quizId":377,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"You have completed watching a video on one of several formats for conducting a Root Cause Analysis.  Based on the statement by the ‘nurse’ in the scenario: “Our high volume of scheduled patients, and then walk-in sick visits are a set up for errors without a specific plan.”  Determine which step of a Root Cause Analysis process was performed by the nurse?\r","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A"]}}},{"id":"si10533","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide10532q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10544","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"g ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide10532q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_126","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_126","title":"Conducting or Participating in a Root Cause Analysis ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_54","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_54","title":"View Scenario ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide10532q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si15269","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"View Scenario ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide10532q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si15289","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"View Scenario ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide10532q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_135","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_135","title":"4 / 17 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10342","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1","title":"In the video on one of several format for conducting a Root Cause Analysis, the NP suggests revising the protocol statement to say: “all children under the age of 6-years with a +PPD must have a referral to the Department of Health (DOH)”. What is the most appropriate NEXT step in conducting an effective Root Cause Analysis?  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10353","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_2","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10357","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_5","title":"Develop causal statements ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10353_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"2","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Develop causal statements\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si10364","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_6","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10368","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_7","title":"Determine when to re-evaluate outcomes ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10364_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"4","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Determine when to re-evaluate outcomes\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si10375","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_8","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10379","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_9","title":"Assign a supervisor to implement the plan ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10375_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"6","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Assign a supervisor to implement the plan\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si10386","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_10","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10390","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_11","title":"End the meeting ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10386_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"8","roles":{"answer":{"title":"End the meeting\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si10433","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_1","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide10532q1","for":"Slide10532q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10445","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide10532q1","for":"Slide10532q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10457","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide10532q1","for":"Slide10532q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10488","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_1","title":"Correct - After creating a plan of action a summary is made and shared with the team. The summary includes when to re-evaluate outcomes.   Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide10532q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10519","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_3","title":"The correct answer is B - After creating a plan of action a summary is made and shared with the team.  The summary includes when to re-evaluate outcomes.   Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide10532q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si15961","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide10532q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide10532","class":"Question Slide","instance":"Question 2","thumbnail":"","children":["si5613","si5626","si5639","si5666","si5672","si10070","si10533","si10544","Text_Caption_126","SmartShape_54","si15269","si15289","Text_Caption_135","si10342","si10357","si10368","si10379","si10390","si10433","si10445","si10457","si15961"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide10532"},"question":{"interactionId":"10328","quizId":377,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"In the video on one of several format for conducting a Root Cause Analysis, the NP suggests revising the protocol statement to say: “all children under the age of 6-years with a +PPD must have a referral to the Department of Health (DOH)”. What is the most appropriate NEXT step in conducting an effective Root Cause Analysis?\r\r","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"]}}},{"id":"si10808","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide10807q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10819","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"g ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide10807q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_51","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_51","title":"Conducting or Participating in a Root Cause Analysis ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_136","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_136","title":"5 / 17 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10617","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_12","title":"The interprofessional team in the video conducted a Root Cause Analysis.  Which of these statements best represents the group interactions? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10628","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_13","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10632","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_14","title":"The team members demonstrated interprofessional respect for one another which is a part of the Interprofessional Collaborative Practice core competencies (IPEC).   ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10628_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"2_9","roles":{"answer":{"title":"The team members demonstrated interprofessional respect for one another which is a part of the Interprofessional Collaborative Practice core competencies (IPEC).  \r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si10639","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_15","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10643","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_16","title":"One member of the team seemed to dominate the conversation which is the way most Root Cause Analyses should be conducted.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10639_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"4_10","roles":{"answer":{"title":"One member of the team seemed to dominate the conversation which is the way most Root Cause Analyses should be conducted. \r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si10650","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_17","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10654","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_18","title":"The decision to correct the problem focused on clinical competencies rather than on team interactions. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10650_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"6_11","roles":{"answer":{"title":"The decision to correct the problem focused on clinical competencies rather than on team interactions.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si10661","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_19","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10665","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_20","title":"The team leader encouraged team members to identify team members who performed the error so new protocols could be made. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10661_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"8_12","roles":{"answer":{"title":"The team leader encouraged team members to identify team members who performed the error so new protocols could be made.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si10708","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_2","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide10807q2","for":"Slide10807q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10720","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide10807q2","for":"Slide10807q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10732","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide10807q2","for":"Slide10807q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10763","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_5","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide10807q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10794","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_6","title":"Incorrect Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide10807q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si15982","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide10807q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide10807","class":"Question Slide","instance":"Question 3","thumbnail":"","children":["si5613","si5626","si5639","si5666","si5672","si10070","si10808","si10819","Text_Caption_51","Text_Caption_136","si10617","si10632","si10643","si10654","si10665","si10708","si10720","si10732","si15982"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide10807"},"question":{"interactionId":"10603","quizId":377,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"The interprofessional team in the video conducted a Root Cause Analysis.  Which of these statements best represents the group interactions?\r","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"]}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_125","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_125","title":"Click here if video does not load ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Web_2","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Web_2","roles":{}},{"id":"SmartShape_39","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_39","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_40","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_40","title":"f ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_41","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_41","title":"g ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_42","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_42","title":"____ ____ ____ ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_6","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_6","roles":{}},{"id":"Text_Caption_130","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_130","title":"Scenario: Root Cause Analysis ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_47","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_47","title":"Return to last slide visited ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si14774","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Return to last slide visited ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si14794","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Return to last slide visited ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_137","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_137","title":"6 / 17 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide10870","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"Incorrect Scenario","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_125","SmartShape_39","SmartShape_40","SmartShape_41","SmartShape_42","Image_6","Text_Caption_130","SmartShape_47","si14774","si14794","Text_Caption_137"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide10870"}}},{"id":"si11181","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide11180q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11192","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"g ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide11180q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_52","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_52","title":"Conducting or Participating in a Root Cause Analysis - ‘Gone Wrong’ ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_52","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_52","title":"View Scenario ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide11180q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si15117","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"View Scenario ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide11180q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si15137","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"View Scenario ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide11180q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_138","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_138","title":"7 / 17 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10959","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_21","title":"You have completed watching a video showing an In-Correct way to conduct a Root Cause Analysis.  In the video, The team leader states how he is “really upset” about the complaints from the Department of Health (DOH). Which of the following steps of a Root Cause Analysis is being performed? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10970","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_22","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10974","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_23","title":"Identifying feelings ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10970_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"13","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Identifying feelings\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si10981","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_24","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10985","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_25","title":"Causal statements  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10981_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"15","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Causal statements \r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si10992","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_26","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10996","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_27","title":"Identifying what happened ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10992_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"17","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Identifying what happened\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si11003","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_28","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11007","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_29","title":"Acting as a team leader  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11003_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"19","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Acting as a team leader \r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si11050","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_3","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide11180q3","for":"Slide11180q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11062","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide11180q3","for":"Slide11180q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11074","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide11180q3","for":"Slide11180q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11105","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_7","title":"Correct -  The complaints from the DOH is identifying the adverse event.  The Team Leader is not using effective communication skills by stating he is “really upset.”   Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide11180q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11136","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_8","title":"The correct answer is C - The complaints from the DOH is identifying the adverse event.  The Team Leader is not using effective communication skills by stating he is “really upset.”    Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide11180q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si15995","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide11180q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide11180","class":"Question Slide","instance":"Question 4","thumbnail":"","children":["si5613","si5626","si5639","si5666","si5672","si10070","si11181","si11192","Text_Caption_52","SmartShape_52","si15117","si15137","Text_Caption_138","si10959","si10974","si10985","si10996","si11007","si11050","si11062","si11074","si15995"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide11180"},"question":{"interactionId":"10945","quizId":377,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"You have completed watching a video showing an In-Correct way to conduct a Root Cause Analysis.  In the video, The team leader states how he is “really upset” about the complaints from the Department of Health (DOH). Which of the following steps of a Root Cause Analysis is being performed?\r","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["C"]}}},{"id":"si11430","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide11429q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11441","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"g ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide11429q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_54","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_54","title":"Conducting or Participating in a Root Cause Analysis - ‘Gone Wrong’ ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_55","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_55","title":"View Scenario ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide11429q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si15345","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"View Scenario ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide11429q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si15365","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"View Scenario ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide11429q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_139","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_139","title":"8 / 17 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11239","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_30","title":"Which of the following statements made by team members in the video is indicative of causal statements? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11250","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_31","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11254","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_32","title":"Mistakes happen and the Department of Health will understand.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11250_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"13_20","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Mistakes happen and the Department of Health will understand.\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si11261","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_33","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11265","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_34","title":"Mistakes just do not happen – people make mistakes!  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11261_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"15_21","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Mistakes just do not happen – people make mistakes!\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si11272","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_35","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11276","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_36","title":"We are just too busy and should limit patient visits per day.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11272_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"17_22","roles":{"answer":{"title":"We are just too busy and should limit patient visits per day.\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si11283","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_37","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11287","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_38","title":"High patient volume is a setup for errors without a specific plan.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11283_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"19_23","roles":{"answer":{"title":"High patient volume is a setup for errors without a specific plan.\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si11330","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_4","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide11429q4","for":"Slide11429q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11342","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide11429q4","for":"Slide11429q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11354","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide11429q4","for":"Slide11429q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11385","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_9","title":"Correct -  This response states how the high volume of patients and lack of plan caused the adverse event.   Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide11429q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11416","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_10","title":"The correct answer is D - This response states how the high volume of patients and lack of plan caused the adverse event.     Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide11429q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16008","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide11429q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide11429","class":"Question Slide","instance":"Question 5","thumbnail":"","children":["si5613","si5626","si5639","si5666","si5672","si10070","si11430","si11441","Text_Caption_54","SmartShape_55","si15345","si15365","Text_Caption_139","si11239","si11254","si11265","si11276","si11287","si11330","si11342","si11354","si16008"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide11429"},"question":{"interactionId":"11225","quizId":377,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"Which of the following statements made by team members in the video is indicative of causal statements?\r","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["D"]}}},{"id":"si11736","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide11735q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11747","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"g ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide11735q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_55","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_55","title":"Conducting or Participating in a Root Cause Analysis - ‘Gone Wrong’ ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_56","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_56","title":"View Scenario ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide11735q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si15421","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"View Scenario ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide11735q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si15441","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"View Scenario ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide11735q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_140","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_140","title":"9 / 17 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11514","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_39","title":"In the video the Nurse Practitioner states that she remembers a missed PPD follow-up in the past. This is indicative of: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11525","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_40","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11529","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_41","title":"Recurrence of error ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11525_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"13_24","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Recurrence of error\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si11536","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_42","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11540","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_43","title":"NP negligence ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11536_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"15_25","roles":{"answer":{"title":"NP negligence\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si11547","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_44","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11551","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_45","title":"Failed protocol ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11547_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"17_26","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Failed protocol\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si11558","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_46","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11562","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_47","title":"Poor teamwork ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11558_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"19_27","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Poor teamwork\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si11605","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_5","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide11735q5","for":"Slide11735q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11617","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide11735q5","for":"Slide11735q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11629","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide11735q5","for":"Slide11735q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11660","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_11","title":"Correct -  The team should conduct as Root Cause Analysis.  The past error signifies that this is a recurring error.   Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide11735q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11691","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_12","title":"The correct answer is A - The team should conduct as Root Cause Analysis.  The past error signifies that this is a recurring error.  Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide11735q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16021","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide11735q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide11735","class":"Question Slide","instance":"Question 6","thumbnail":"","children":["si5613","si5626","si5639","si5666","si5672","si10070","si11736","si11747","Text_Caption_55","SmartShape_56","si15421","si15441","Text_Caption_140","si11514","si11529","si11540","si11551","si11562","si11605","si11617","si11629","si16021"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide11735"},"question":{"interactionId":"11500","quizId":377,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"In the video the Nurse Practitioner states that she remembers a missed PPD follow-up in the past. This is indicative of:\r","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A"]}}},{"id":"si12086","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide12085q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12097","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"g ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide12085q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_56","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_56","title":"ROOT CAUSE ANALYSIS QUESTIONS: APPLICATION/ANALYSIS QUESTIONS  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_141","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_141","title":"10 / 17 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11864","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_48","title":"Three patients report they were not notified about laboratory results this week.  Protocol states that patients are notified via mail about lab results. Which of the following would be the most appropriate INITIAL question? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11875","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_49","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11879","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_57","title":"Why weren’t the patients notified?  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11875_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"13_28","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Why weren’t the patients notified?\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si11886","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_58","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11890","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_59","title":"Do we have the correct addresses?  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11886_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"15_29","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Do we have the correct addresses?\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si11897","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_60","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11901","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_61","title":"Are the labs accessible in the chart?  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11897_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"17_30","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Are the labs accessible in the chart?\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si11908","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_62","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11912","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_63","title":"How can we prevent this from recurring? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11908_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"19_31","roles":{"answer":{"title":"How can we prevent this from recurring?\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si11955","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_6","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide12085q6","for":"Slide12085q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11967","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide12085q6","for":"Slide12085q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11979","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide12085q6","for":"Slide12085q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12010","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_14","title":"Correct -  The first step of a root cause analysis is to identify what happened and then to open up a conversation with the team to discuss it. Asking why the patients weren’t notified allows the team to identify what happened.  Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide12085q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12041","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_15","title":"The correct answer is A - The first step of a root cause analysis is to identify what happened and then to open up a conversation with the team to discuss it. Asking why the patients weren’t notified allows the team to identify what happened.  Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide12085q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16034","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide12085q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide12085","class":"Question Slide","instance":"Question 7","thumbnail":"","children":["si5613","si5626","si5639","si5666","si5672","si10070","si12086","si12097","Text_Caption_56","Text_Caption_141","si11864","si11879","si11890","si11901","si11912","si11955","si11967","si11979","si16034"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide12085"},"question":{"interactionId":"11842","quizId":377,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"Three patients report they were not notified about laboratory results this week.  Protocol states that patients are notified via mail about lab results. Which of the following would be the most appropriate INITIAL question?\r","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A"]}}},{"id":"si12374","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide12373q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12385","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"g ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide12373q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_64","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_64","title":"ROOT CAUSE ANALYSIS QUESTIONS: APPLICATION/ANALYSIS QUESTIONS  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_58","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_58","title":"View Scenario ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide12373q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si15573","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"View Scenario ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide12373q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si15593","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"View Scenario ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide12373q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_142","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_142","title":"11 / 17 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12152","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_65","title":"Multiple patients patients were identified who received meningococcal vaccinations that were prepared with the wrong diluent.  Which of the following is the BEST intervention to prevent recurrence of this event? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12163","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_66","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12167","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_67","title":"Create a new vaccine protocol  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12163_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"13_32","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Create a new vaccine protocol\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si12174","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_68","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12178","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_69","title":"Recall vaccinated patients  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12174_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"15_33","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Recall vaccinated patients\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si12185","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_70","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12189","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_71","title":"Conduct a Root Cause Analysis  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12185_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"17_34","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Conduct a Root Cause Analysis\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si12196","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_72","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12200","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_73","title":"Identify who administered the vaccines  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12196_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"19_35","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Identify who administered the vaccines\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si12243","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_7","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide12373q7","for":"Slide12373q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12255","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide12373q7","for":"Slide12373q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12267","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide12373q7","for":"Slide12373q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12298","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_17","title":"Correct -  A Root Cause Analysis is performed to improve systems and prevent recurrence of adverse events.  Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide12373q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12329","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_18","title":"The correct answer is C - A Root Cause Analysis is performed to improve systems and prevent recurrence of adverse events.  Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide12373q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16047","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide12373q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide12373","class":"Question Slide","instance":"Question 8","thumbnail":"","children":["si5613","si5626","si5639","si5666","si5672","si10070","si12374","si12385","Text_Caption_64","SmartShape_58","si15573","si15593","Text_Caption_142","si12152","si12167","si12178","si12189","si12200","si12243","si12255","si12267","si16047"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide12373"},"question":{"interactionId":"12130","quizId":377,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"Multiple patients patients were identified who received meningococcal vaccinations that were prepared with the wrong diluent.  Which of the following is the BEST intervention to prevent recurrence of this event?\r","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["C"]}}},{"id":"si12662","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide12661q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12673","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"g ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide12661q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_74","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_74","title":"ROOT CAUSE ANALYSIS QUESTIONS: APPLICATION/ANALYSIS QUESTIONS  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_143","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_143","title":"12 / 17 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12440","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_75","title":"Multiple patients were diagnosed with catheter related UTI’s on the same unit within the past month.  What is the most appropriate intervention? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12451","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_76","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12455","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_77","title":"Conduct a Root Cause Analysis  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12451_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"13_36","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Conduct a Root Cause Analysis\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si12462","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_78","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12466","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_79","title":"Educate staff on catheter placement  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12462_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"15_37","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Educate staff on catheter placement\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si12473","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_80","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12477","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_81","title":"Use sterile technique   ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12473_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"17_38","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Use sterile technique \r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si12484","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_82","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12488","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_83","title":"Develop causal statements.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12484_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"19_39","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Develop causal statements.\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si12531","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_8","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide12661q8","for":"Slide12661q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12543","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide12661q8","for":"Slide12661q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12555","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide12661q8","for":"Slide12661q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12586","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_20","title":"Correct -  A Root Cause Analysis is conducted to analyze errors and adverse events to prevent recurrence.  Since this error has been identified in the past and has recurred it is important that the team conducts a Root Cause Analysis.   Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide12661q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12617","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_21","title":"The correct answer is C - A Root Cause Analysis is conducted to analyze errors and adverse events to prevent recurrence.  Since this error has been identified in the past and has recurred it is important that the team conducts a Root Cause Analysis.   Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide12661q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16060","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide12661q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide12661","class":"Question Slide","instance":"Question 9","thumbnail":"","children":["si5613","si5626","si5639","si5666","si5672","si10070","si12662","si12673","Text_Caption_74","Text_Caption_143","si12440","si12455","si12466","si12477","si12488","si12531","si12543","si12555","si16060"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide12661"},"question":{"interactionId":"12418","quizId":377,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"Multiple patients were diagnosed with catheter related UTI’s on the same unit within the past month.  What is the most appropriate intervention?\r","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A"]}}},{"id":"si12950","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide12949q9"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12961","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"g ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide12949q9"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_84","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_84","title":"GENERAL RECALL ROOT CAUSE ANALYSIS QUESTIONS  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_144","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_144","title":"13 / 17 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12728","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_85","title":"The PURPOSE of a Root Cause Analysis is to: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12739","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_86","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12743","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_87","title":"Identify who made the error.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12739_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"13_40","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Identify who made the error.\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si12750","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_88","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12754","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_89","title":"Identify why the error occurred.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12750_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"15_41","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Identify why the error occurred.\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si12761","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_90","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12765","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_91","title":"Identify when the error occurred.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12761_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"17_42","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Identify when the error occurred.\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si12772","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_92","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12776","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_93","title":"Identify how to prevent the error.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12772_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"19_43","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Identify how to prevent the error.\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si12819","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_9","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide12949q9","for":"Slide12949q9"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12831","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide12949q9","for":"Slide12949q9"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12843","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide12949q9","for":"Slide12949q9"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12874","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_23","title":"Correct -  The purpose of conducting a Root Cause Analysis is to prevent recurrence of an adverse event.   Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide12949q9"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12905","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_24","title":"The correct answer is D - The purpose of conducting a Root Cause Analysis is to prevent recurrence of an adverse event.  Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide12949q9"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16073","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide12949q9"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide12949","class":"Question Slide","instance":"Question 10","thumbnail":"","children":["si5613","si5626","si5639","si5666","si5672","si10070","si12950","si12961","Text_Caption_84","Text_Caption_144","si12728","si12743","si12754","si12765","si12776","si12819","si12831","si12843","si16073"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide12949"},"question":{"interactionId":"12706","quizId":377,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"The PURPOSE of a Root Cause Analysis is to:\r","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["D"]}}},{"id":"si13238","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide13237q10"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13249","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"g ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide13237q10"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_94","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_94","title":"GENERAL RECALL ROOT CAUSE ANALYSIS QUESTIONS  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_145","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_145","title":"14 / 17 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13016","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_95","title":"Which of the following is MOST descriptive of a Root Cause Analysis? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13027","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_96","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13031","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_97","title":"Identify people involved  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13027_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"13_44","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Identify people involved\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si13038","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_98","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13042","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_99","title":"Express frustration ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13038_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"15_45","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Express frustration\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si13049","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_100","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13053","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_101","title":"Generate a list of actions ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13049_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"17_46","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Generate a list of actions\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si13060","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_102","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13064","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_103","title":"Create disciplinary measures ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13060_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"19_47","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Create disciplinary measures\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si13107","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_10","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide13237q10","for":"Slide13237q10"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13119","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide13237q10","for":"Slide13237q10"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13131","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide13237q10","for":"Slide13237q10"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13162","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_26","title":"Correct -  Generating a list of actions to prevent recurrence of an error or adverse event is a step in a Root Cause Analysis.    Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide13237q10"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13193","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_27","title":"The correct answer is D - Generating a list of actions to prevent recurrence of an error or adverse event is a step in a Root Cause Analysis.   Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide13237q10"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16086","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide13237q10"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide13237","class":"Question Slide","instance":"Question 11","thumbnail":"","children":["si5613","si5626","si5639","si5666","si5672","si10070","si13238","si13249","Text_Caption_94","Text_Caption_145","si13016","si13031","si13042","si13053","si13064","si13107","si13119","si13131","si16086"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide13237"},"question":{"interactionId":"12994","quizId":377,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"Which of the following is MOST descriptive of a Root Cause Analysis?\r","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["D"]}}},{"id":"si13526","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide13525q11"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13537","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"g ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide13525q11"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_104","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_104","title":"GENERAL RECALL ROOT CAUSE ANALYSIS QUESTIONS  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_146","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_146","title":"15 / 17 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13304","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_105","title":"In order to reduce harm in the clinical setting it is MOST important to analyze: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13315","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_106","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13319","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_107","title":"People ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13315_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"13_48","roles":{"answer":{"title":"People\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si13326","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_108","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13330","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_109","title":"Communication ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13326_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"15_49","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Communication\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si13337","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_110","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13341","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_111","title":"Errors ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13337_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"17_50","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Errors\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si13348","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_112","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13352","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_113","title":"Systems ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13348_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"19_51","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Systems\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si13395","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_11","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide13525q11","for":"Slide13525q11"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13407","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide13525q11","for":"Slide13525q11"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13419","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide13525q11","for":"Slide13525q11"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13450","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_29","title":"Correct -  A Root Cause Analysis takes a systematic approach to analyzing errors and reducing harm.     Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide13525q11"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13481","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_30","title":"The correct answer is D - A Root Cause Analysis takes a systematic approach to analyzing errors and reducing harm.    Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide13525q11"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16099","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide13525q11"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide13525","class":"Question Slide","instance":"Question 12","thumbnail":"","children":["si5613","si5626","si5639","si5666","si5672","si10070","si13526","si13537","Text_Caption_104","Text_Caption_146","si13304","si13319","si13330","si13341","si13352","si13395","si13407","si13419","si16099"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide13525"},"question":{"interactionId":"13282","quizId":377,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"In order to reduce harm in the clinical setting it is MOST important to analyze:\r","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["D"]}}},{"id":"si13814","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide13813q12"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13825","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"g ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide13813q12"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_114","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_114","title":"GENERAL RECALL ROOT CAUSE ANALYSIS QUESTIONS  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_147","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_147","title":"16 / 17 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13592","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_115","title":"A child who weighs 40 lbs was prescribed ibuprofen 600 mg. No adverse reaction occurred and the medication was discontinued.  All of the following are reasons to conduct a Root Cause Analysis, EXCEPT: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13603","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_116","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13607","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_117","title":"Determine what should have happened   ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13603_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"13_52","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Determine what should have happened \r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si13614","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_118","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13618","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_119","title":"To identify the prescriber and provide disciplinary action  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13614_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"15_53","roles":{"answer":{"title":"To identify the prescriber and provide disciplinary action\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si13625","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_120","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13629","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_121","title":"Determine cause   ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13625_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"17_54","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Determine cause \r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si13636","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_122","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13640","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_123","title":"Generate a list of recommended actions to prevent recurrence of the event  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13636_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"19_55","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Generate a list of recommended actions to prevent recurrence of\rthe event\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si13683","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_12","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide13813q12","for":"Slide13813q12"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13695","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide13813q12","for":"Slide13813q12"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13707","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide13813q12","for":"Slide13813q12"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13738","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_32","title":"Correct -  All of the above except for B are steps in a Root Cause Analysis     Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide13813q12"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13769","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_33","title":"The correct answer is D - All of the above except for B are steps in a Root Cause Analysis  Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide13813q12"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16112","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide13813q12"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide13813","class":"Question Slide","instance":"Question 13","thumbnail":"","children":["si5613","si5626","si5639","si5666","si5672","si10070","si13814","si13825","Text_Caption_114","Text_Caption_147","si13592","si13607","si13618","si13629","si13640","si13683","si13695","si13707","si16112"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide13813"},"question":{"interactionId":"13570","quizId":377,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"A child who weighs 40 lbs was prescribed ibuprofen 600 mg. No adverse reaction occurred and the medication was discontinued.  All of the following are reasons to conduct a Root Cause Analysis, EXCEPT:\r","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"]}}},{"id":"si13885","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13896","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"f ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13907","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"g ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13918","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"____ ____ ____ ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13929","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si14052","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Scenario: Root Cause Analysis ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_5","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_5","roles":{}},{"id":"Text_Caption_127","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_127","title":"Thank you for completing the Root Cause Analysis sub-module! ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_35","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_35","title":"Exit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si14022","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Exit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si14042","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Exit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_148","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_148","title":"17 / 17 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_149","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_149","title":"This Online Learning Module is supported by the Health and Human Resources Administration (HRSA) of the U.S. Department of Health and Human Services (HHS) as part of an award totaling $2.1 million with no percentage financed with non-governmental sources. The contents are those of the author(s) and do not necessarily represent the official views of, any endorsement, by HRSA, HHS, or the U.S. Government.  Principal Investigator: Donna Hallas PhD, PPCNP-BC, NPNP, PMHS, FAANP HRSA GRANT # D09HP29976 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide13868","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si13885","si13896","si13907","si13918","si13929","si14052","Image_5","Text_Caption_127","SmartShape_35","si14022","si14042","Text_Caption_148","Text_Caption_149"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide13868"}}},{"id":"Pool421","class":"pool","roles":{"pool":{"id":421,"name":"Pool1","questions":[]}}},{"id":"Root Cause Analysis","class":"project","title":"Root Cause Analysis","children":["Slide9896","Slide9973","Slide10103","Slide10532","Slide10807","Slide10870","Slide11180","Slide11429","Slide11735","Slide12085","Slide12373","Slide12661","Slide12949","Slide13237","Slide13525","Slide13813","Slide13868"],"roles":{"quiz":{"id":377,"branched":false,"submitAll":false,"review":true,"questions":["Slide10103q0","Slide10532q1","Slide10807q2","Slide11180q3","Slide11429q4","Slide11735q5","Slide12085q6","Slide12373q7","Slide12661q8","Slide12949q9","Slide13237q10","Slide13525q11","Slide13813q12"],"minScore":0,"maxScore":0,"passScore":0}}}],"contentSettings":{"global":{"branchAware":false},"toc":{"navigationEnabled":true,"navigateVisitedSlides":false,"collapseAll":false,"showTopicDuration":false,"statusFlag":false,"selfPaced":true,"showSearch":false,"enabled":true},"playbar":{"enabled":false,"cc":false,"playPause":true,"back":true,"forward":true,"rewind":true,"close":true,"mute":true,"progressBar":true}},"contentReporting":{"CCCriteria":"launch_content","SCCriteria":"launch_content","exitNormalIfCompleted":false},"toc":[{"id":"Slide9896","title":"Introduction","visible":true},{"id":"Slide9973","title":"Correct Scenario","visible":true},{"id":"Slide10103","title":"Question 1","visible":false},{"id":"Slide10532","title":"Question 2","visible":false},{"id":"Slide10807","title":"Question 3","visible":false},{"id":"Slide10870","title":"Incorrect Scenario","visible":true},{"id":"Slide11180","title":"Question 4","visible":false},{"id":"Slide11429","title":"Question 5","visible":false},{"id":"Slide11735","title":"Question 6","visible":false},{"id":"Slide12085","title":"Question 7","visible":false},{"id":"Slide12373","title":"Question 8","visible":false},{"id":"Slide12661","title":"Question 9","visible":false},{"id":"Slide12949","title":"Question 10","visible":false},{"id":"Slide13237","title":"Question 11","visible":false},{"id":"Slide13525","title":"Question 12","visible":false},{"id":"Slide13813","title":"Question 13","visible":false},{"id":"Slide13868","title":"Exit/Summary","visible":false}]}